Proper golf course etiquette is a very, very important part of the golf game.
My name is Jared Garbett with Echo Farms Country Club, and I'm going to teach you how to practice proper golf etiquette.
Before arriving at the course, you need to call ahead and make a tee time.
This lets the golf course know that you're coming, so that they don't book somebody else in your spot.
You also want to check for any specific regulations that the golf course may have, as far as dress code, wearing proper golf attire, collared shirts, pants, and what types of shoes you need to wear.
Making sure that you play fast whenever you get to the golf course is extremely important as well.
You should never take any more than four and a half hours to play eighteen holes of golf.
While you're out on the course, you want to make sure you're quiet while other people are hitting.
You want to make sure that you never stand in front of anybody as they get ready to hit their golf shot.
Whenever it's your turn to hit your shot, you need to make sure that you're ready and you take your time when hitting the shot, but do not take any more time than you need.
Just being generally respectful of the people in your group, the people in front of and the people behind you, is perfect.
Just practice the golden rule.
Do unto others as you would have them do unto you.
Don't hit into the group in front of you, and don't hold up the group behind you.
That's how you practice proper golf etiquette.